<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Essay on StackGrandiose</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/essay/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Essay on StackGrandiose</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/essay/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My Antonia</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/my-antonia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/my-antonia/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/posts/&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;&amp;ndash; Back&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I always wanted to read &lt;em&gt;My Ántonia&lt;/em&gt;. Not because I was aware of the story, but because of the cover. My paperback copy is this small, reddish-maroon book with WPA-Era art adorning the cover. The overall look of this book made me think that this book would be interesting.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If I could describe this book in very broad terms, I would say it is a coming of age story of a young man who grows up in Nebraska and how that childhood shapes the person he is. The book being titled &lt;em&gt;My Ántonia&lt;/em&gt; is in reference to a bohemian girl named Ántonia who grows up in parallel with the main character, Jim Burden.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Catcher in the Rye Review</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/catcher/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/catcher/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/posts/&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;&amp;ndash; Back&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you have never read &amp;ldquo;The Catcher in the Rye&amp;rdquo; before, one may think that the book is a sophisticated piece of fiction that should be classified in the same category as celebrated 19th century&#xA;stories. It should surely be a difficult to read yet highly insightful body of work. Even if not everyone thinks these things, it is certainly what I thought when I first decided to read&#xA;&amp;ldquo;The Catcher in the Rye&amp;rdquo;. However, my preassumed opinions of the book were quickly ruined when the very first paragraph was written as a teenager complaining. This guy was complaining about his&#xA;parents being &amp;ldquo;touchy as hell&amp;rdquo; and his brother being a supposed prostitute.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alien Essay</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/alien/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/alien/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/posts/&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;&amp;ndash; Back&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This is a essay that I wrote for school. It is pretty long &amp;amp; wordy some of the stuff I do not totally agree with, and it assumes things through a secular world view. Its main purpose being here is to see what a large amount of&#xA;text will look like on this website.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;an-argument-for-extraterrestrials-existence&#34;&gt;An Argument for Extraterrestrial’s Existence&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Throughout generations of humanity, the desire to find out if our life-rich planet is alone has been strong. With the advent of modern scientific inventions, our species has been able to scan the stars to hopefully get confirmation that we are not alone. With recent advancements in technology, we now know that there are hundreds of confirmed planets that show promise of carrying life, with theoretically billions of others with similar conditions. These planets do not always mirror Earth’s environment exactly, but certain organisms on Earth prove that extraterrestrials can exist in very extreme places. Basic life definitely exists in the universe (in the form of basic unicellular or multicellular organisms), but complex, intelligent life is exceedingly rare and far away. There are planets that are capable of supporting life, and they are in abundance. Life can exist in eclectic forms, which expands the possibility of where life is. However, the likelihood of intelligent evolving from otherwise nonliving material is uncommon, leading to intelligent life being rare yet existing.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
